<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Living Green Solutions]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Living Green Solutions]]></description>
        <link>http://7-green.com/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2017 06:04:12 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="http://7-green.com/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2017 06:03:53 GMT</pubDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Contact Us]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1><strong>Contact Us</strong></h1>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/bf9cee81-27a4-4099-b907-995bbfc342a9.jpg">]]></description>
            <link>http://7-green.com/contact-us/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">acebc1e2-d1fe-4b3f-9ec1-59daf6bdd976</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2017 03:27:21 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Commercial Maintenance Programs]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h2><strong>Commercial Maintenance Programs</strong></h2>,<p>We know that the responsibilities of today's property managers are great. With security, budgeting and demanding tenants, time management becomes a major focus. We cannot reduce those problems but can lessen the amount of time you will need to spend managing your landscape with our maintenance services.</p>,<p>7-Green will maintain all aspects of your exterior and interior green space maintenance. We will monitor the health of your landscape, as well as, offer you ideas on how to enhance your overall landscape for the long term.</p>,<p>7-Green specializes in maintaining offices, parks, homes, hotels, holiday rentals, industrial parks, and hospitality.</p>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/c206d472-b714-490d-9bcc-e056a2c5d5a3.jpg">]]></description>
            <link>http://7-green.com/2041de09-d5d2-45cc-b1b2-52c2b2e74395/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2041de09-d5d2-45cc-b1b2-52c2b2e74395</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2017 03:10:38 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Commercial]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h2><strong>Commercial</strong></h2>,<p>At 7-Green, we understand that well-maintained common areas, attractive landscaping and a pleasant overall environment are essential to the quality of life for any commercial property. For more than 10 years, we have provided commercial landscaping services for property management and development needs. We help clients achieve their goals on time, efficiently, and at a competitive prices.</p>,<p>Good commercial landscape design is part form and part function. The design should enhance the overall look and image of your building but the design elements should also serve a functional purpose. In order to make the landscape work for you, think about how you want people to interact with your property and what you want them to think about your business.</p>,<p>At 7-Green our landscape design can help you achieve the following:</p>,<p>1. <strong>Convey the right message</strong>. Your business or your building has a brand and your landscape can speak to that. If you want to convey an image, whether it be soothing, healing, sustainable, fun, professional, or edgy and forward thinking, there are landscape elements that can translate that message. Examples include Zen features for soothing spaces; dancing fountains for fun outdoor spaces; native grasses and wildflower plantings and green roofs for sustainability focused buildings, or minimalist geometric plant designs for edgy businesses.</p>,<p>2. <strong>Help people engage with your business.</strong> Your landscape design can either encourage people to stay longer and linger or it can keep them moving along. If you add benches, tables and chairs, fountains and low walls for seating, people will stay and enjoy the outdoor space. Many businesses and hospitality venues have found success creating more elaborate outdoor lounge areas with fire pits and lawn games to encourage people to stay longer.</p>,<p>3. <strong>Direct the flow of traffic.</strong> Most businesses want to direct people to entrances and that can be done by highlighting the entrance points with plants and trees, by creating paths and walkways lined with shrubs or trees, or by using brick or stone wall features. Those elements make bold visual statements in addition to performing an important function.</p>,<p>4. <strong>Attract clients.</strong> If your landscaping makes a bold statement, or offers places to sit that feel inviting, you can attract people to your business. The opposite is true too; if there is little to no shade or there is no pizazz to your landscaping or things aren’t well maintained, you can turn customers away.</p>,<p>5. <strong>Accentuate the architecture.</strong> So much time and thought is spent on the architecture of a building, but the story shouldn’t end there. You can really accentuate your building with the landscaping. Add drama to the front entrance with careful color and texture choices and accentuate the driveway with lines of trees and shrubs. Don’t forget the beauty plants can bring inside; interior plant design, including green walls, can add drama to courtyards and atriums.</p>,<p>6. <strong>Conserve water and energy.</strong> You can also design your landscaping so that it contributes to energy savings by shading your building in the summer. Adding a green roof to your building helps control water run-off and reduces associated energy costs.</p>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/f4d4bac6-3cbb-4759-8a6b-303ce7dc1294.jpg">,<p>Clearpoint - Colombo</p>,<p>7-Green are primary landsape contractor for the stunning Clearpoint green development.</p>]]></description>
            <link>http://7-green.com/61446445-7db0-4dbd-b50e-7a744b570c6b/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">61446445-7db0-4dbd-b50e-7a744b570c6b</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2017 03:06:21 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hello, I'm Harinda]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://imgflo.herokuapp.com/graph/2b2431f8e7ba7b0/697da3d6efce18c13ae12fde4ee836ab/croprotate.jpg?cropheight=1715&cropwidth=3264&degrees=0&input=https%3A%2F%2Fthe-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com%2Fd1f2bf87-f19a-4891-94f4-8d83981877f5.jpg&x=0&y=0" title="Hello, I&apos;m Harinda" alt="My life has been a love affair with Sri Lankas flora and fauna. I grow every indigenous plant in my own nursery. I have written numerous book on the plants and animals that inhabit this beautiful island, I lecture in 300 schools every year on environmental preservation and appreciation. 7-Green is my company and over the last 10 years we have been involved in some amazing projects from major commercial installations to small private gardens on a tight budget and have loved them all. I would love to help you with your project big or small. Contact us and we can see if we can create something together. ">]]></description>
            <link>http://7-green.com/617737fd-c13a-4a59-b791-d9a17a420b34/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">617737fd-c13a-4a59-b791-d9a17a420b34</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2016 11:17:53 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>